Dheeraj Singh

Tech Lead

dheeraj.ips@gmail.com

Summary

I've over 8+years of experience,in Java language, with multiple frameworks-Spring MVC, Spring Restful web services, Google Guice, Jersey Web Services with consumer and produces the JSON or XML.I deliver high quality, clean, working code, quickly and correctly. I'm comfortable with structured code, databases, OO programming, and "specialty" languages such as might be found in workflow or business rules systems.

Experience

Tech Lead
June 2015 - Present

Sr.Software Engineer
June 2013 - May 2015 (2 years)

Software Engineer
June 2009 - May 2013 (4 years)

Education

Rajiv Gandhi Prodyogiki Vishwavidyalaya Master of Computer Applications - MCA, 2006 - 2009 Devi Ahilya Vishwavidyalaya B.Sc. IT (Information Technology), Information Technology, 2002 - 2005

Dheeraj Singh

Tech Lead

dheeraj.ips@gmail.com



Contact Dheeraj on LinkedIn